dyclassroom.com 2019-04-06

# Privacy - DYclassroom | Have fun learning :-)

Last modified: 10 November 2016

Privacy policy for DYclassroom

You don't have to sign up to use DYclassroom website.

You will be asked to enter your name, email address and/or your website link ONLY when you create your account on our website.

However, DYclassroom website is FREE and you don't have to register to use it.

To improve our site based on the information collected and feedback that we receive.

We use cookies, like most of the websites on the world wide web. Cookies are small files that are saved on your computer or mobile phone or tablet when you visit website. We use cookies to understand site traffic and offer better user experience.

Learn more about [cookies](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie).

We don’t use cookies

  * To collect any personally identifiable information or sensitive information (without your permission)
  * To pass personally identifiable information to third parties

If you are using our website then you are granting us the permission to use cookies. Though, you can deactivate cookies on your browser but doing so will make most of the modern websites stop working correctly, including this one.

We use Google Analytics on our website to better understand the traffic on our website.

We use Google Custom Search on our website to allow our users to search content on our website. This uses cookies to serve ads.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our website.

Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings.](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/)

In order to run and maintain our website we run advertisements provided by ad providing partners like Google AdSense. These partners place cookies and collect anonymous data based on the websites visited to serve personalise adverts.

Our website contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

By using our website you agree to our privacy policy.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes here on this page. If you have any question regarding the Privacy Policy, please feel free to [contact us](https://www.dyclassroom.com/contact).
